Guide to the James Lockhart Autry Family Papers, 1832-1998 MS 003
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
James Lockhart Autry Family Papers
1832-1998
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Autry, James Lockhart, II
MS 003
84 Linear Feet (100 boxes and oversize materials)
Business papers, correspondence, photographs and memorabilia related to the James Lockhart Autry family of Texas (1875-present) and of North Carolina (1832), Tennessee (1824-1840) and Mississippi (1840-1875) show the life style of a family who moved into Texas and played an important role in developing both the social and economic framework of Houston. Among the business papers are correspondence and legal briefs from the terms Autry served as general counsel to the Texas Company, president of Fidelity Trust Company, and vice-president and general counsel of the American Republics Corporation.
Biographical Note
James Lockhart Autry, II was born in Holly Springs, Mississippi, on November 4, 1859. Educated in Mississippi schools for most of his life, Autry attended the University of the South on a scholarship before moving to Texas in 1876. He moved to Navarro County to undertake management of a ranch given to his grandfather's heirs for his part in the Texas Revolution.
Once established in Texas, Autry began the study of law in the offices of Judge Sam Frost in Corsicana, and was admitted to the bar in 1880 at the age of twenty-one. While still studying law in 1879, Autry served as enrolling clerk for the House of Representatives of the Texas Legislature and he served again in the sessions of 1880 and 1881. Autry began the practice of law in partnership with Richard Channing Beale; he retired from this partnership, however, to serve two terms as County Judge of Navarro County. He then formed a partnership with W. J. McKie which lasted until Autry left Corsicana to become General Attorney for the Texas Company in Beaumont.
The partnership of McKie and Autry served as counsel to J.S. Cullinan, an oil operator who moved into Corsicana with the oil boom of the area during the 1890's. After the dissipation of oil in the Corsicana area and the discovery of oil in the Spindletop - Beaumont area, Cullinan moved to the coastal town to form the Texas Fuel Company. For several years McKie and Autry continued to serve Cullinan, taking turns on leaving Coriscana to spend one or two weeks at a time in Beaumont. Finally in 1904 the partnership of McKie and Autry was dissolved with McKie staying in Corsicana and Autry moving to Beaumont as general counsel of the Texas Fuel Company.
A reorganization and expansion of the Texas Fuel Company in 1905 resulted in the incorporation of the Texas Company in which Autry was elected a director and became general attorney. The corporate headquarters were moved to Houston in 1908 when Spindletop began to decline and other fields down the Gulf Coast like Humble and Goose Creek began to produce. Autry again moved with the company. He remained with the Texas Company until November of 1913 when a dispute over management of the company became a major issue in a stockholders' meeting and a proxy struggle ensued. Cullinan with the open support of Autry and Will C. Hogg lost the battle and resigned as president and director. Autry and Hogg both resigned at this time.
Autry, Cullinan and Hogg then combined their capital and talents to form the Fidelity Trust Company, Farmers Petroleum Company, American Petroleum Company and Republic Production Company. Autry served as president of Farmers Petroleum Company, president of Fidelity Trust Company and vice-president and general counsel of the last two under the combined name of American Republics Company. In 1915 Autry suffered a stroke and he spent the last five years of his life a semi-invalid seeking rehabilitation and use of his right side. He died on September 29, 1920. He was survived by his wife, the former Allie Kinsloe, whom he married in 1896, a son James Lockhart Autry III, and a daughter Allie May Autry.
Allie Belle Kinsloe Autry was born in Corsicana, Texas in 1873. She married James Lockhart Autry II in 1896. Throughout her life she was active in philanthropic causes in Corsicana and Houston. In 1921 she donated money for the construction of a community house at Rice Institute. A memorial to her husband, Autry House served as social meeting place for students, faculty, and campus organizations at Rice Institute. She also donated $50,000 towards the establishment of a hospital school for children with tuberculosis, Autry Memorial Hospital School, as a memorial to her son, James Lockhart Autry III. She died in 1935.
James Lockhart Autry, III was born in Corsicana, Texas 1899. The only son of James Lockhart Autry II, he graduated from Rice Institute in 1921. After graduation he was the vice-president of the American Supply Company. He died after complications from appendicitis at the age of 23.
Allie May Autry Kelley was the second child of James L. Autry II and Allie Kinsloe Autry. She was born 1903 in Corsicana, Texas. She graduated from Rice Institute in 1925, the first woman in her family to attend college. As a student at Rice she was extremely popular, elected class vice president 1921-22 and 1924-25, queen of May Fete 1925 and was a lifelong supporter of her alma mater. She helped establish Autry Court, the Allie Kelley Dittmar lounge in the student center, and generously supported the Friends of the Fondren Library. She married Edward Watson Kelley in 1935 and had two children, Edward "Mike" Watson Kelley, Jr and Allie Autry Kelley Dittmar. She died in 1998 at the age of 94.
Scope and Content
The collection contains business papers, correspondence, photographs, and memorabilia of the James Lockhart Autry family. Among the business papers are correspondence and legal briefs from the terms Autry served as general counsel to the Texas Company, president of Fidelity Trust Company, and vice-president and general counsel of the American Republics Corporation.
Family papers include correspondence from Autry's grandfather Micajah Autry (1792-1836) to his wife describing his travels to Texas. Micajah Autry came to Texas to fight in the revolution and died at the Alamo. Autry's father, James Lockhart Autry, served as Speaker of the House of Representatives in Mississippi and practiced law in partnership with Lucius Cincinnatus Lamar. A number of papers deal with this aspect of his career as well as his service in the Confederate Army in which he attained the rank of Lieutenant Colonel and was killed at the Battle of Murfreesboro on December 31, 1862. Also included are correspondence from Autry's mother, Jeanie Valliant Autry Brown to her immediate family.
The bulk of the collection pertains to James Lockhart Autry II's business papers, legal papers, numbered files, personal papers, memorabilia, and papers dealing with administration of his estate.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research. Researchers may only use photocopies of Micajah Autry letters.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Acquisition Information
The papers were a gift of Mrs. Edward W. Kelley and her daughter Allie Autry Kelley Dittmar. Date Received: Summer 1959. An addendum to the collection was received from Mrs. Edward W. Kelley and her granddaughter Kelley Dittmar in 1989 and 1992.
General note
Portions of this collection are available online at https://scholarship.rice.edu/handle/1911/68495
Related Archival Materials
See also Rice University architectural drawings, oversize manuscript material, maps and photographs, UA 226.
See also Kelley Industries Inc. business records, 1936-1986, MS 102, http://library.rice.edu/collections/WRC/finding-aids/manuscripts/0102
Index Terms
Subjects
Revolution (Texas: 1835-1836); Petroleum industry and trade; Business
Document Types
financial records; corrrespondence; scrapbooks; photographs; legal documents; diaries
Places
Autry House (Houston, Tex.); Westmoreland Farms (Houston, Tex.); Texas -- History
Subjects (Persons)
Autry, Micajah; Autry, James Lockhart, II; Autry family
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University; Mexico Fuel Oil Company; Fidelity Insurance, Trust and Safe Deposit Company; Texas Company; Texas Land & Abstract Company; Texas Fuel Company; American Republics Corporation
- Series I: North Carolina, 1728-1824, 148140
  - Theophilus Autry, 1728-1824; 148144
    - Will of Theophilus Autry (photocopy), [1832]; 148649 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Series II: Tennessee, 1824-1840, 148141
  - Micajah Autry, 1794-1836; 148145
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Researchers may only use photocopies of Micajah Autry letters.
    - Correspondence - M[icajah] Autry to Mrs Martha W. Autry, 1834 Feb. 11; 814; ALS (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - M. Autry to Mrs. Martha W. Autry, 1834 Feb. 16; 813; ALS (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - M. Autry to Mrs. Martha W. Autry, 1835 Dec. 7; 812; ALS (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - M. Autry to Mrs. Martha W. Autry, 1835 Dec. 13; 811; ALS (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Copy of the Muster Roll, Nacogdoches, Texas, 1836 Jan. 14; 810; ALS (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Obituary of Major Micajah Autry, [1836 Feb. 28]; 809; Clipping (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Land grant by Anson Jones to the heirs Micajah Autry, 1846 Feb. 5; 804; Photocopy (Drawer 81)
  - Martha Wyche Putney Wilkerson Autry, 1794-1866; 148146
    - Obituary of Mrs. Amelia W. Smith, [1836]; 807; Clipping (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Nat. G. Smith to Mrs. Amelia W. Smith, [1836]; 808; ALS (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Photographs - Tintype of Martha Wyche Autry, 148683 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Series III: Mississippi, 1840-1875, 148142
  - Martha Wilkerson Autry, 1794-1866; 148147
    - Correspondence - James L. Talbot to Mrs. Micajah Autry, 1856 Sept. 11; 783; ALS (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - D.W.C. Smith to Mrs. Martha W. Autry, 1856 Nov. 27; 778; ALS (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - D.W.C. Smith to James L. Autry, 1856 Oct. 9; 782; ALS (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - DeWitte C. Smith to James L. Autry, 1858 Mar. 10; 757; ALS (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - Bill of Sale to D.W.C. Smith, 1858 Apr. 3; 755; DS (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - DeWitte C. Smith to James L. Autry, 1858 Jul. 18; 754; ALS (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - D.W.C. Smith to James L. Autry, 1860 Jun. 3; 742; ALS (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - D.W.C. Smith to James L. Autry, 1862 Oct. 2; 720; ALS (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Photograph of Dewitt Clinton Smith, n.d., 148652 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Mary Autry Greer, 1827-1915; 148148
    - Correspondence - John Autry to Mary Autry, 1839 Dec. 29; 806; ALS (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - Mary A. Greer to James L. Autry, 1851 Mar. 16; 797; ALS (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - Mary A Greer to James L. Autry, 1856 Nov. 9; 781; ALS (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - James M. Greer to Mrs. Martha W. Autry, 1856 Dec. 17; 772; ALS (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - James M. Greer to Martha W. Autry, 1856 Dec. 18; 771; ALS (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - Rev. J.T. Pickett to Mrs. [M.A.] Greer and Mrs. [J.V.] Autry, 1866 Apr. 1; 701; ALS (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - D. Edward Greer to James L. Autry, [1872] Feb [16]; 684; ALS (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - Maggie F. Greer to James L. Autry, 1873 Sept. 30; 680; ALS (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence - Maggie F. Greer to James L. Autry, [1873]; 677; ALS (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - "Sketch of my Life," by Mary Autry Greer, n.d.; 637; photocopy (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - "Siege of the Alamo," and other sketches by Mary Autry Greer, 148675 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Obituary of Mary Autry Greer, May 31, 1915; 148650 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Photograph of Mary Autry Greer, n.d.; 148676 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Col. James Lockhart Autry, 1830-1862; 148149
    - Correspondence, 1842-1862; 148653
      - John Autry to James L. Autry, 1842 Apr. 12; 805; ALS (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Arthur Clayton to James L. Autry, 1846 Apr. 30; 803; ALS (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - [Elihu K.] Valliant to [James L.] Autry, 1848 Feb. 7; 802; ALS (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Jas. R. Chalmer to Jas. L. Autry, Mar. 22 [1849-1850]; 646; ALS (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - D.C. Glenn to James L. Autry, 1850 Nov. 12; 800; ALS (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - J.L. Autry to Martha W. Autry, 1851 Apr. 1; 796; ALS (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - [James Harper] Starr and [Nathanial C.] Amory to James L. Autry, Including Proof of Heirship of Autry, 1851 Jun. 18; 795; ALS (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - James R. Armstrong to James L. Autry, 1851 Oct. 21; 794; LS (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - William F. Henderson to James L. Autry, 1851 Nov. 4; 793; ALS (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - L. Smith to James L. Autry, 1851 Nov. 27; 792; ALS (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - Edward C. Walthall to James L. Autry, 1852 Feb. 22; 791; ALS (Box 1, Folder 43)
      - R.L. Watson to James L. Autry, 1852 Jun. 22; 790; ALS (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - James R. Armstrong to James L. Autry, 1853 Feb. 9; 789; LS (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1855 Sept. 18; 787; ALS (Box 1, Folder 46)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1855 Sept. 28; 786; ALS (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - J.B. Lockhart to James L. Autry, 1856 Jul. 9; 784; ALS (Box 1, Folder 48)
      - B.D. McKie to James L. Autry, 1856 Nov. 19; 780; ALS (Box 1, Folder 49)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs M.W. Autry, 1856 Nov. 26; 779; ALS (Box 1, Folder 50)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1856 Nov. 30; 777; ALS (Box 1, Folder 51)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1856 Dec. 2; 776; ALS (Box 1, Folder 52)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1856 Dec. 8; 775; ALS (Box 1, Folder 53)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.A. Greer, 1856 Dec. 14; 774; ALS (Box 1, Folder 54)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1856 Dec. 17; 773; ALS (Box 1, Folder 55)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1856 Dec. 21; 770; ALS (Box 1, Folder 56)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1856 Dec. 28; 769; ALS (Box 1, Folder 57)
      - Invitation to a Bridal Party Honoring Col. and Mrs. Edward Pickett, 1857 Jan. 7; 768 (Box 1, Folder 58)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1857 Jan. 11; 767; ALS (Box 1, Folder 59)
      - James L. Autry to James M. Greer, Jr., 1857 Jan. 16; 766; ALS (Box 1, Folder 60)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1857 Jan. 25; 764; ALS (Box 1, Folder 61)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1857 Jan. 29; 763; ALS (Box 1, Folder 62)
      - H. Whitehorn to James L. Autry, 1857 Aug. 10; 762; ALS (Box 1, Folder 63)
      - Jesse Taylor to James L. Autry, 1858 Mar. 10; 756; ALS (Box 1, Folder 64)
      - Catharine A. McWillie to James L. Autry, 1858 Aug. 18; 753; ALS (Box 1, Folder 65)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1858 Nov. 7; 751; ALS (Box 1, Folder 66)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1858 Nov. 17; 750; ALS (Box 1, Folder 67)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1858 Dec. 1; 747; ALS (Box 1, Folder 68)
      - L.Q.C. Lamar [Jr.] to James L. Autry, 1858 Dec. 15; 746; ALS (Box 1, Folder 69)
      - L.Q.C. Lamar [Jr.] to James L. Autry, [1858]; 148651 (Box 1, Folder 70)
      - James L. Talbot to James L. Autry, 1859 Jan. 14; 745; ALS (Box 1, Folder 71)
      - Telegram from Talbot to James L. Autry, 1860 May 25; 743; DS (Box 1, Folder 72)
      - H.C. Anthony, W.L. Martin & R.J. Allison to James L. Autry, 1860 Jun.30; 741; ALS (Box 1, Folder 73)
      - C.H. Mott to Autry, Walter, & Mickle, 1861 Mar. 21; 740; ALS (Box 1, Folder 74)
      - Jas. L. Autry to Jas. L. Autry, Jr., 1861 Apr. 11; 739; ALS (Box 1, Folder 75)
      - J.L. Autry to Jeanie V. Autry, [ca.1861]Apr.12; 738; ALS (Box 1, Folder 76)
      - H.A. Cooke to James L. Autry, 1861 Apr. 12; 737; ALS (Box 1, Folder 77)
      - James L. Autry to James M. Greer, 1861 Apr. 12; 736; ALS (Box 1, Folder 78)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1861 Apr. 12; 735; ALS (Box 1, Folder 79)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. Mary A. Greer, 1861 Apr. 20; 734; ALS (Box 1, Folder 80)
      - James R. Chalmers to James L. Autry, 1861 Sept. 9; 729; DS (Box 1, Folder 81)
      - J.P. Benjamin to James L. Autry, 1862 Feb. 13; 724; DS (Box 1, Folder 82)
      - James L. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1862 May 13; 722; ALS (Box 1, Folder 83)
      - Wedding invitation to Col. and Mrs. James L. Autry, [1862] Oct. 16; 719; ALS (Box 1, Folder 84)
      - James L. Autry to General S. Cooper, 1862 Oct. 29; 718; LS (Box 1, Folder 85)
      - A.L.C. Magruder to Col. James L. Autry, 1862 Nov. 13; 716; ALS (Box 1, Folder 86)
      - James Autry to Jeanie V. Autry, 1862 Nov. 17; 715; ALS (Box 1, Folder 87)
      - General Bragg, George G. Garner to James L. Autry, 1862 Nov. 30; 714; DS (Box 1, Folder 88)
      - Alexander F. Martin to James L. Autry, 644; ALS (Box 1, Folder 89)
      - Miscellaneous Social Notes to James L. Autry, n.d.; 635 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Political Career, 1850-1859; 148654
      General
      James Lockhart Autry served as a representative to the Mississippi Legislature from Marshall County from 1854-1859. He was also elected Speaker of the House 1857-1859.
      - Speech [by James L. Autry], [ca.] 1850; 799; AD (Box 1, Folder 91)
      - Address [by James L. Autry], [ca.] 1850; 798; AD (Box 1, Folder 92)
      - Address Delivered by J.L. Autry at the Marshall Female Institute, 1855 Jun. 28; 788; AD (Box 1, Folder 93)
      - Broadside Advertising Political Meeting, 1856 Mar. 8; 785 (Box 1, Folder 95)
      - Reply to a toast delivered by J.L. Autry at a Supper of the Alumni of St. Thomas Hall, 1857 Dec. 24; 761; AD (Box 1, Folder 96)
      - Address delivered by J.L. Autry, July 4 [prior to 1858]; 760; AD (Box 1, Folder 97)
      - Speech [written by James L. Autry], [prior to 1858]; 759; AD (Box 1, Folder 98)
      - Address by J.L. Autry Welcoming Col. [Jefferson] Davis, [prior to 1858]; 758; AD (Box 1, Folder 99)
      - Acceptance Speech by J.L. Autry to the Mississippi House of Representatives Accepting Position of Speaker of the House, [1858 Nov.]; 748; AD (Box 1, Folder 100)
      - Speech by J.L. Autry to the Literary Societies of Semple Broaddus College, 1859 Jun. 22; 744; AD (Box 1, Folder 101)
      - Newspaper clipping mentioning James L. Autry, n.d.; 148677 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Civil War, 1861-1862; 148655
      James Lockhart Autry served as lieutenant colonel of B/F-S, 9th Regiment, Mississippi Infantry. After reorganization in spring 1862, Autry became lieutenant colonel of the 27th Regiment, Mississippi Infantry. He was killed during the Battle of Murfreesboro on December 31, 1862. His promotion to general, signed by President Jefferson Davis, was on its way to Autry at the time of his death.
      Source: The hour of our nation's agony: the Civil War letters of Lt. William Cowper Nelson of Mississippi. Edited by Jennifer W. Ford, 2007.
      - Isaac N. Edwards to H.M. Walters, 1861 Sept. 6; 733; ALS (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Capt. T.F. Kerr to Lt. H.W. Walter, 1861 Sept. 7; 732; ALS (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Dr. W.J. Price about Capt. Kerr, 1861 Sept. 7; 731; ALS (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Arthur Clayton, H.T. Scott, James T. Lester, E. Murrell, and H.C. MacLaughlin to Lt. H.W. Walter, 1861 Sept. 8; 730; DS (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Court of Inquiry into the Actions of Capt. Kerr, 1861 Sept. 11; 728; DS (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Brig. Gen. S.H. Gladden to Gen. Cooper, 1862 Jan. 21; 725; ALS (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Gen. Braxton Bragg to Pres. Jefferson Davis, 1862 Feb. 21; 723; ALS (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Braxton Bragg to Maj. Gen. Van Dorn, 1862 Jun. 25; 721; DS (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - A.A.G. John G. Deverean to Lt. Gen. Pemberton, 1862 Nov. 5; 717; DS (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Gen. Bragg and George G. Garner to Capt. I.B. Sale, 1862 Dec. 5; 713; DS (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Order for Officer of the Day, 1862 Dec. 20; 712; DS (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Partial List (copied) of Names of Officers of the 9th and 27th Mississippi Regiments, [ca. 1861-1862]; 711; DS (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Chattanooga Daily Rebel, vol. 1, no. 262, Front Page, 1863 Jun. 9; 708 (Drawer 81)
    - Miscellaneous, 148673
      - Bill of William F. Henderson against the Estate of Micajah Autry, 639; DS (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Professional Card of James L. Autry, n.d.; 638; Card (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Photographs of James Lockhart Autry (oversized removed Oversize Materials series), ca. 1861; 148674 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        Locket with photograph of James L. Autry inside and strands of hair.
      - Photograph of Mrs. Lucy Holcomb Pickens in frame with notation by James L. Autry, A distinguished and beautiful Southern woman., 1853; 154256 (Box 43)
  - Jeanie Valliant Autry Brown, 1833-1916; 151685
    - Correspondence - Jeanie V. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry ALS, November 1, 1858; 151686 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - Jeanie V. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry, 1858 Nov. 20; 151687 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - Jeanie V. Autry to Mary A. Greer ALS, 1861 Sept. 25; 151688 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - [Jeanie V. Autry] letter ALS, [1861] Sept. 11; 151689 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - J. J. Govan to Mrs. James L. Autry ALS, 1863 Jan. 30; 151690 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - [M]ary P. G[ovan] to Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry ALS, [1863] Apr. 25; 151691 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Mary P. Govan to Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry ALS, [1863]; 151692 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - Fanny Y. (Mrs. A.) Craft to Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry ALS, [1863]; 151693 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - [Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry to Mrs Mary A. Greer] ALS, 1864 May 1; 151694 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - Mr. B. Mickle to Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry ALS, 1864 Jul. 18; 151695 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - Accounts from Addison Craft to Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry DS, 1866 Feb. [20-7]; 151696 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - Circuit Court of Marshall Co., Miss. to Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry, 1866 April 19; 151697 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence - George B. Myers to Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry ALS, 1866 Apr. 19; 151698 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence - Kinloch Falconer to Mrs. J. V. Autry ALS;DS, 1866 June 7; 151699 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry to Mrs Jas. M. Greer ALS, 1866 Jun. 20; 151700 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence - Johnson, Denegre & Penn to Mrs Jeanie V. Autry ALS, 1866 Nov. 26; 151701 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence - Masonic Lodge No. 35 to Mrs. James L. Autry DS, [1866]; 151702 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence - Mr. Jo Caruthers to Mrs. J.V. Autry ALS, 1870 Feb.; 151703 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence - Bishop W.M. Green to Mrs. J.V. Autry ALS, 1873 Jun. 27; 151704 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence - Hode to Aunt Jeanie V. Autry ALS, 1873 Jun. 27; 151705 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence - Ann Worthington to Mrs. J.V. Autry ALS, 1873 Aug. 31; 151706 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence - Gen. J. Gorgas to Mrs. J.V. Autry ALS, 1874 Apr. 12; 151707 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Jeanie V. Brown to James L. Autry ALS, 1881 Feb. 11; 151708 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Jeanie V. Brown to James L. Autry ALS, 1881 Feb. 13; 151709 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry to Mrs. M.W. Autry n.d. ALS, 151711 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry to Mr. Jas. M. Greer n.d. ALS, 151712 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Jeanie V. Autry to Mrs. Mrs. Mary A. Greer n.d. ALS, 151713 (Box 2, Folder 42)